(Sunlight slowly spreads throughout the sky.)
(It's the perfect weather for a new start.)
("'Sixth Sense,' The New Season is Here")
(Sixth Sense is back.)
("'Sixth Sense' Official on the Sunday Variety Program Schedule")
Are we filming? I think we are.
- Song Eun I?
- Hello.
- I love you.
- Thank you.
You're so pretty.
I love you.
- Have a good day.
- Thank you.
Eun I.
- Kyung Pyo. Have you been well?
- Have you been well?
I've been good.
Why is everyone looking younger?
That can't be.
(Laughing)
- I mean...
- Is it that you got older?
(Teasing each other right away like siblings)
So I was saying...
(Original Sixth Sense member, Yu Jae Seok)
- So I was saying, CEO Song...
- So I was saying...
Someone came and grabbed her face.
- What?
- An elderly woman was passing by,
grabbed my face, and said, "Oh, Song Eun I."
- I was so surprised.
- She said I was cute.
You're still adored.
I am, of course, by the elderly.
- Yes.
(Meanwhile, at a cafe in Guro)
It's been forever since I've been a regular member on a show.
- Has it been that long?
- Yes.
I hope I can do well.
(This nervous person waiting for the other members is...)
(A new Sixth Sense member, BIBI)
("Bam Yang Gang," "BUMPA," and more)
(From a singer who dominates the stage with stand-out songs...)
(to an actress who mastered intense action scenes!)
(She even proved her reasoning abilities...)
(on "High School Mystery Club.")
(A true all-rounder, the new Sixth Sense member, BIBI)
Oh, "BUMPA" is here.
(Singing a welcome song as he enters)
- It's been so long.
- It really has.
- Long time no see.
- You've gotten even cooler.
Nice to see you.
- We need some drinks.
- Yes, some drinks.
Wait, what do they have?
- I'd like an iced Americano.
- Of course.
You're really a CEO, having a coffee in the morning.
- I don't so much lately, - Have some.
- but I want to be alert today.
- Right. Maybe a decaf.
By the way...
From the back... Did you get the same haircut?
Hey, why would I get the same cut as him of all people?
(Nice and round, They do look kind of similar?)
- Seriously.
- Didn't you copy Dex's hair?
I'm so offended.
(Getting worked up)
The Dex cut suits you well.
- Really?
- Kind of like my hair, right?
- Shall we sit?
- Yes.
Now that we have BIBI here...
Have you met Kyung Pyo?
- This is our first time.
- You're meeting for the first time.
- Really?
- Nice to meet you.
BIBI, I'm sure you all know...
From "BUMPA" to "Bam Yang Gang..."
(A true treasure who can sing and act well)
You know, I...
I love her acting in dramas.
- Seriously.
- She's so good at acting.
- I met her once on a set,
- and I told her I was a big fan.
- I see.
- Thank you.
- BIBI is no joke.
- Yes.
- I don't know what to do.
- What?
- Why do you keep...
- Don't be too nice?
- What should we do?
Why do you keep complimenting me? I have to...
What?
- I have to...
- What?
- Is something down there?
- Hide.
Oh, you're trying to hide.
I was really surprised to hear...
- BIBI would be joining us.
- Seriously.
When we got the offer, everyone at my agency...
all went, "Oh, my gosh!"
- Really?
- Yes.
"Go on 'Sixth Sense!'"
- They said, "Do it, Hyeong Seo."
- Really?
Besides those two, did you also want to join?
Yes, of course. I saw this show a lot on Reels.
It's been too long since I've seen Mi Rae.
- Me too.
- So, they are "those two?"
- Of course.
- Tiger JK and Mi Rae?
Did you think I was referring to the two of us?
- I thought some executives...
- Tiger JK and Mi Rae.
Yes, Tiger JK.
We did Future Liger together.
- Right.
Tiger JK and I are very close.
Oh, really?
Only on social media.
- Tiger JK is always like that.
- Right?
On social media, he's all like, "Sis!"
He sends hearts and stuff.
(Full of emojis)
But when you actually see him, he goes, "Oh, hello..."
Exactly.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
That's interesting.
You were born in 1999, right, BIBI?
- I was born in 1998.
- Oh, 1998.
In 1998, weren't you wearing that mask everywhere?
You were my sister-in-law.
(It wasn't when I was wearing the mask.)
- You were my sister-in-law.
- Right.
- In “My Husband, the Grasshopper.” - Exactly.
- “My Husband, the Grasshopper.” - “My Husband, the Grasshopper.”
(A kid at the time, Born that year, Let's just laugh along.)
You know Kyung Pyo also does a lot of variety shows, right?
Variety shows are my main focus now.
- Good. Do them when you can.
- Exactly.
- They're fun.
Do dramas and movies too...
I enjoyed his drama.
In "Undercover Miss Hong,"
he was acting like he was normal.
Yes, I was on "Undercover Miss Hong,"
- that took over Korea.
- That's right.
He was wearing a suit and acting all normal.
He is an actor, after all.
(Ko Kyung Pyo, Actor, Actually very good at acting)
So, we have to use our intuition on this show.
- Right.
- How is yours?
I don't think it's that good.
- You have bad intuition?
- Yes.
I'm good at collecting evidence, if there is any.
- So I'm a bit...
- It's difficult.
- worried, yes.
- Oh, by the way...
Is this not "City Tour?" Is it a different season?
- This time...
- We changed the subtitle.
- What is it now?
- I see.
- The subtitle is...
- Yes?
"Sixth Sense: B-Side."
- B-Side?
Oh, "Sixth Sense: B-Side?"
B-Side? Why is it B-Side?
- Why?
(B-Side: The other side of side A)
(B-Side: The hidden side beyond what can be seen)
(Last season, we were suspicious.)
(Fake menus)
(Fake owners)
(Fake stores)
(Now, broaden your view...)
(and focus on what's behind.)
(The key clue to finding the fakes, B-Side)
(When you find the B-Sides hidden in various places,)
(you can find the answer inside.)
(Even more blatant)
(Even bolder)
(We'll tell you the answer.)
(When we get it wrong,)
(the staff can really make fun of us.)
(That's why we're telling you.)
(Will you be able to find the answers...)
(we planted on the B-Side?)
That sounds fun.
If you look around...
more carefully than usual,
it'll help you find out what's real and fake.
Last season was already hard...
(That's true.)
Last season, the probability...
My head is starting to hurt.
- We have a topic for episode one.
- What is it?
The topic of episode one...
is, "Don't Believe It Show."
- "Don't Believe It Show?"
- Yes.
"Don't Believe It Show."
(Among three unbelievable shows, find the fake one!)
- I like it.
- So we have...
- some hints for episode one.
- I see.
- What is this?
- We have some tapes.
- Tapes about episode one, I see.
- We didn't have these before.
- What is this?
- It's a real clue.
They must've prepared this specifically for BIBI.
Since she likes evidence.
If you play the B-Side, there'll be a clue.
These are some reactions to people who went to the shows.
- They made audio files...
- Right.
- of reviews people wrote.
- I think so.
(The first show, Audience reaction hint)
It's getting bigger and bigger.
Hey, you're going to pee yourself.
"Getting bigger and bigger?"
- "Getting bigger and bigger."
- "You're going to pee yourself."
- They have to be playing with fire.
- You're right.
- Right? It has to be fire.
- Right.
Or is it something with lots of water?
Something like that?
It's getting bigger and bigger.
Hey, you're going to pee yourself.
(What kind of show is the first show?)
- Shall we listen to the second one?
- Press play.
(The second show, Audience reaction hint)
- Isn't this "Swan Lake?"
- It is.
Hey, that just moved, right?
What? That's moving.
(That's it.)
- What did they say?
- Should we listen to it again?
- I couldn't hear it very well.
- What did they say?
(Let's listen one more time.)
(Music from "Swan Lake")
Hey, that just moved, right?
What? That's moving.
(What's the second show about?)
Okay, hold on. The last one.
(The third show, Audience reaction hint)
(Screaming)
A person is flying around.
(Ha!)
A person is flying around?
- Didn't you hear a gunshot?
- Kind of.
- Right? And a scream.
- Yes.
A person is flying around?
(An unidentifiable gunshot)
(What is the third show with flying people?)
(A person is flying around.)
- What is this?
- Bang, bang!
- "A person is flying around."
- Right?
I guess it's not all food this time.
- I guess so.
It's hard to serve food while flying around.
Right. I'm so curious.
I think we'll have to try to know.
Shall we get going?
The weather is so...
- The weather is so nice.
- It really is.
You like summer, right, BIBI?
- I like summer.
- Summer suits you.
Oh, thank you.
(Learned a Gen Z reaction)
Really? Personally,
I don't love summer.
Same, I actually like winter.
- Right?
- Yes.
- I like autumn the best.
- I see.
- Autumn is the best.
- Autumn is nice.
Spring means summer is coming, so...
(I don't really like it.)
- I like autumn.
- How detailed.
Yes, but autumn is sad...
because it means a year is ending.
- I see.
- Yes.
You're not really listening, are you?
(Guilty)
You just have to say you like autumn,
but you keep explaining why.
- Hello.
- You already shared your opinion,
- but you kept talking. Yes.
"Yes?" You don't know them.
(Almost thought they were neighbours, Acting so friendly to strangers)
Oh, it's not that...
- You don't know them.
- You just had to say...
you like autumn, but...
- Hello.
Wait, where are we going?
Right. They said it was...
- in walking distance.
- Right.
Wait, so the hint for the first show was...
- "You're going to pee yourself."
- Right.
"It's getting bigger and bigger."
- "You're going to pee yourself."
- Is it not food? What is it?
- Seriously.
I'm a bit sad that it's not food.
- It's not food.
- Yes, seriously.
I'm sure one of them is food.
- Yes, at least one.
- I'm sure.
Nothing is decided yet.
- At least one.
BIBI, do you like to eat?
- I love to eat.
- That's why I live.
- You like it that much?
Yes.
Wait, is it here?
What? Hey.
- Isn't this fire?
- You're right.
- There's a bunch of firewood.
- Oh, there's firewood.
(They guessed the tape hint was about playing with fire.)
Isn't this fire?
I think the hint earlier was about playing with fire.
This must be it!
(The store is full of firewood.)
Like a wood-fired grill?
(The first show will take place here!)
- This is food. Right?
- Nice!
- That must be delicious.
- It's firewood.
- I can already smell firewood.
- Yes.
- You can smell it from here.
- You can really smell...
- an oak tree scent.
- Really?
It actually does.
(Looking forward to it)
Is this all right, though?
- It smells like...
- I know, right?
They're mostly in the suburbs.
- Right.
- And outdoors.
- In a private place.
- Exactly.
I wonder what it is.
Should we go inside?
(They enter the first venue.)
(Knocking)
What is it?
- What...
- What's this?
(Amazed)
- It's so pretty!
- Goodness.
Can they do this inside a building?
It's blazing.
It really is a restaurant.
- It is.
- It's blazing.
They can do this inside a building?
It's this big?
- Their kitchen hood is gigantic.
- It is.
(The wood fire shows off its presence.)
I know it's not my concern,
but where is all the smoke going?
I know, right?
That's where this smell is coming from.
- This is fascinating.
- It is, isn't it?
(Welcome to the 1st Don't Believe It Show!)
(Blazing fire...)
(and a table that reminds you of a bonfire)
(There's firewood everywhere,)
(and it's filled with things related to fire and food.)
(What show will they put on here?)
But does this...
make sense?
It feels like I'm finally on Sixth Sense.
I haven't felt this in a long time.
(He turns into a detective.)
I bet it tastes good.
But this is...
This is no joke.
You must like reading the menu too.
I do.
It's my favourite type of book.
It's my reading time.
She suddenly started reading the menu.
(Hyeong Seo's happy reading moment)
They have bone marrow.
- What is it?
- What's that?
It's the inside of an ox bone.
How do you know that?
I'm a foodie.
- Really?
It goes really well with steak.
It adds to the flavour.
- It's like...
- Oh, really?
Yes. The rich flavour of beef tallow.
(This foodie will show off her skills soon.)
Didn't they talk about peeing earlier?
- What?
- Getting bigger. What?
(The restaurant suddenly turned dark.)
What's going on?
(What is happening?)
- They're playing music.
- What is it?
(A man enters while the song plays.)
- What?
- Oh, my.
I think he's going to show us something.
(He quietly takes something out of the fire.)
(Surprised)
Oh, my.
- What's happening?
- Oh, my.
(He puts something into a tool that looks like a bull's horn.)
Isn't it hot?
(The fire gets stronger.)
- What is this?
- What's he doing?
(Exclaiming)
(Liquid falls from the fire.)
He's pouring grease.
(Standing up)
What's wrong with him?
Why...
(The fantastic fire show continues.)
Something's dripping.
- That's grease, right?
- I think so.
- Oh, my.
- No way.
(Watching the fire show from the 1st row)
- Oh, my.
- My gosh.
(They automatically give an applause.)
Hello, everyone.
- Hi.
What is this place?
This is where you come to enjoy campfire in the middle of the city.
You get to dine while watching a performance.
- A performance?
- Yes.
Really?
This restaurant is themed as an urban campsite,
and we entertain guests...
with spectacular fire shows.
(A restaurant where they put on fire shows)
We serve different types of dishes according to the season.
(Various fire shows and course meals depending on the season)
We put on special performances,
so the kitchen is...
our stage.
(The kitchen is their stage.)
(Impressed)
A lot of them visit us for special occasions.
(It's become a popular place for special occasions.)
(- It's always fully booked.
- The steak is perfectly cooked.)
(It's also trending on social media.)
Sixth Sense, do you think this place is real?
(Do you think this place is real?)
We sell the experience of fire...
through our performances.
- "The experience of fire."
- Yes.
Here,
the fire tower and the kitchen are our stage.
The chefs are the actors,
and our customers are the audience.
That was what we had in mind when we designed it.
Did you get the equipment from a flea market?
The tools are called "flambadou,"
which is a cooking tool...
used back in the day in Southwest France.
It's actually hard to come by.
(Hot fat catches fire, creating flames that enhance the flavour.)
We secured a client in Europe...
- and brought them here.
- Really?
The thing that dripped from the tool was...
meat fat?
Yes, butter, fat,
and herbs.
It catches fire and instantly infuses the meat with flavour.
(It creates smoky oil.)
Do we cover the steak with it?
- Yes, you first mix...
- The herbs smell so good.
the beef tartare with a spoon.
Then, you can put as much as you want on the bread.
Is that so?
The first dish is Korean beef tartare.
Fresh Korean female beef...
and caviar.
(Caviar)
Topped with assorted vegetables and aioli sauce.
We use a special tool called the flambadou...
to add a special flavour.
(Oil drips from flambadou,)
(and it adds a smoky scent.)
Mix all the ingredients of the tartare...
and put as much as you want on a piece of bread.
(You eat it with bread.)
(The first dish, Korean beef tartare)
It's beef tartare, but it's slightly cooked.
It smelled smoky as soon as I put my spoon in it.
Yes, it smells smoky all of a sudden.
(Smoky)
Even the different sauces...
- have the smoky scent.
- Right?
- It smells so good.
- That's interesting.
I've never had anything like this.
People these days must be so happy.
- They have such good food.
- Aren't you one of them?
Right.
(You're pretty young too.)
(The youngest one tries it right away.)
It's so tasty.
- Do you like it?
- It's so good.
Oh, no.
- The extra scent...
- Yes.
deepens the flavour.
It does taste like fire.
That smoky scent...
And it's not too much.
It's so subtle.
You're right.
- It's delicious.
- It certainly...
suits the palate of a young one.
BIBI is stamping her feet so hard under the table.
(Stamping her feet)
(Tasty food makes BIBI dance.)
- I'm glad I'm on this show.
- Are you happy?
I made the right choice. I'm so happy.
(A big bite)
- It's really good.
- It's...
something I've never tasted before.
I've never tasted anything like it.
I'll show you the next dish, grilled shrimp.
I love it.
They're doing something over there.
The second dish is grilled shrimp.
We topped grilled shrimp...
with compound butter...
infused with smoked paprika and gochujang.
- That's butter?
- Oh, my gosh.
(He picks up gochujang butter.)
(It's showtime!)
(Impressed)
- Goodness.
- Look at it dripping!
I mean,
you could just spread it on top.
He had to melt it with fire.
It makes it look like the fire is dancing.
- It's literally a show.
- Right.
(While the fire dances,)
(paprika and gochujang butter drips down.)
- All the dishes are so fancy.
- Yes.
(The second dish, grilled shrimp)
Seriously.
(Sniffing)
- Thank you.
- This butter smells so unique.
- It also smells like curry.
- Yes!
- Like Indian curry, right?
- Yes.
(Kyung Pyo tries it first.)
It's good.
(While everyone is enjoying it,)
(he's struggling.)
(Exclaiming)
I personally think...
you should peel the whole shrimp if you're going to.
I'd say I made it really easy to peel them.
I see. You heard that?
I guess you heard that.
So, you're just bad at peeling shrimp.
Most people can do it.
I hate having to peel my food.
(Taking a bite)
There's a famous story.
One day, Jae Seok invited...
his junior comedians for a meal, so they went.
And his mom made like 20 dishes.
Everyone was so amazed...
and dying to eat them, and Jae Seok suddenly said,
"Mom, do we have ramyeon?"
I prefer ramyeon over my mom's cooking.
It may sound ungrateful, but...
So, they were all shocked.
You can put all sorts of delicacies on the table,
and what I want at that moment is my delicacy.
(The owner came back with something.)
The next dish is our main steak.
(The main dish is here.)
That's not dry ice. It's the smell of charcoal.
- It's smoked.
- It's so aromatic.
(Startled)
With the bones?
That's bone marrow.
- Oh, that's bone marrow?
- Yes.
- Is that it?
The third dish, the main dish, is Korean heifer steak.
We grilled it alongside bone marrow...
in our custom wood-fired oven.
(Steaks and bone marrow cooked in a wood-fired oven)
Chimichurri is a signature South American sauce...
made with herbs and a touch of acidity.
(A subtle smoky aroma by adding burnt rosemary)
(The third dish, Korean heifer steak)
Excellent.
You can't eat steaks like this at home.
Right.
It smells so good.
- That's...
- Rosemary.
- Yes, rosemary, right?
- Yes.
- Is that gravy?
- It is.
(It's gravy sauce.)
(You're so good at this!)
- What was that, BIBI?
- You sound so smart.
- What's this called?
- Gravy.
- Gravy?
- Yes.
(A bunch of gravy with that meaty flavour)
- Heifer steak?
- It looks good.
It's made of South American herbs...
- Chimichurri!
- Yes, we added that.
They all look so expensive.
You two respond so differently.
BIBI is so glad to see them,
and Jae Seok is like, "They look expensive."
"Very expensive."
(Let's give them a try.)
- Very expensive.
I bet it's good.
- And it's cooked perfectly.
- Yes.
(It's cooked to perfection!)
Let's find out.
(How will it taste?)
What do you think?
(Moaning)
(Satisfied)
- Let's see.
- And it's cooked perfectly.
- Yes.
- I'm serious.
- Right?
- It's medium...
(Exclaiming)
This is the main dish.
- Is it? The steak?
- Yes.
It's definitely the main dish.
(BIBI, the foodie,)
(puts chimichurri on top.)
- Is it? The steak?
- Yes.
It's definitely the main dish.
(Laughing)
- I knew it was good.
- How is it?
(Happy)
The price doesn't feel right, though.
- Wait. How much was it?
- Right.
The course is 98 dollars for dinner.
- It's 98 dollars?
- That's right.
That sounds reasonable for a full-course meal.
- Yes.
- Right.
I'm surprised that it's cheaper than it looks.
When you consider the labour costs...
Exactly.
(The price is too low considering its quality and quantity.)
I don't think...
this restaurant usually serves this kind of food.
When you look at all the equipment, there are shelves.
Maybe they serve Texas barbecue that has to be cooked...
on different shelves.
(Kyung Pyo's guess)
(It's a Texas barbecue place, not a fire show place?)
I see.
Meat that needs a long time to cook.
Now that he said that,
all he did was pour oil on top.
He didn't actually cook.
- Right. They all came...
- They brought it out.
- Yes.
- from the kitchen.
(All the dishes were already cooked...)
(before leaving the kitchen.)
Could he be an actor?
- He could be.
- Maybe he is.
Now that you say that, he said,
"You're the audience, and I'm performing."
(The fire tower and the kitchen are our stage.)
(The chefs are the actors.)
(And our customers are the audience.)
- That might be true.
- Yes, what he said!
He might have been telling the truth.
He was tipping us off.
And when we get it wrong,
it's a great source to mock us.
- Exactly!
- Yes.
It's so easy for the crew to mock us.
- They had already told us.
- He was acting...
- on Sixth Sense.
- Yes.
We have to keep suspecting...
(The chef appears at that moment.)
I never knew you'd come.
(Flustered)
Did he come out to correct us?
This is our dessert.
We have another fire show for it.
- Is that cheese?
- No, it's dessert.
Did you bring the meringue on purpose?
To call us morons?
(Are you morons?)
- "These morons."
- You just couldn't help it.
- It was right on time.
- You see what I mean?
Yes.
But the food is really delicious.
(The chef gets ready for another fire show.)
- Is that oil?
- It's alcohol.
- Whiskey?
- Yes.
(He uses fire for dessert too?)
(A scoop of whiskey that caught on fire)
You're putting fire on top?
- He's burning the surface.
- Yes.
It's called a Baked Alaska.
The inside is filled with ice cream or cake,
while the outer meringue layer contains air pockets...
that act as thermal insulation.
So, when heat is applied,
the meringue toasts while the ice cream remains cold.
(The final dish, Baked Alaska)
I'll come back with your dessert.
Why would you take it back?
(Doubtful)
He keeps...
- He keeps acting suspiciously.
- Right?
- Maybe that's all he practised.
- What do you think?
He doesn't show us everything.
He demonstrated on one, and now we have four.
- That's the end of the course.
- Okay.
The last one is our signature event.
It's fire gazing.
You can space out while watching the fire.
(Thank you.)
Thank you.
- Thank you for the meal.
- Thank you.
When he did it here,
- it looked too burnt...
- What's happening?
(The lights went off again.)
(As you were leaving, you said to me)
He's suddenly playing "Bam Yang Gang."
(The fire gazing began with "Bam Yang Gang...")
(in the background.)
(Let's be mesmerized by the flames in the middle of the city.)
You can't help but stare into the fire.
I can't help it.
(I love fire gazing.)
(It's a perfect moment with some sweet dessert.)
The fact that we can do this in the middle of the summer...
- is fascinating.
- Yes!
It's so romantic. I love it.
- The temperature is...
- Just right.
- Yes, it is.
- It's pleasant.
(Mesmerized by the bonfire)
When...
couples come here, I bet they kiss.
(Laughing)
Is that coming from experience?
I bet a lot of them kiss during this.
(Watch out for this kissing gourami.)
- You've never kissed before.
- I mean...
You can dim the lights too.
It'd be so funny if you added a kissing moment.
Yes.
- There's ice cream inside.
- Yes.
It's smokey ice cream.
This ice cream tastes familiar, though.
Is this Gugu Cluster?
- That's what it tastes like.
- Yes.
Once it starts looking suspicious, everything looks fake.
- Right?
Every time, he does a short demonstration...
and comes back with four dishes from the kitchen.
(It's like magic that copies 4 dishes.)
Why don't we move to the second one?
- Great idea.
- Yes.
(The fire-show restaurant)
- Thank you for the food.
- Thank you for the food!
Thank you!
Definitely.
- Oh, my gosh.
- Oh, my.
- That startled me.
- Oh, man.
When did they all go up there?
I have no idea.
- You're so handsome!
- Hi!
(Citizens heard the news and came to watch.)
- Hi, everyone.
- No way.
I'm afraid we have to move.
- Do we get in this van?
- Yes.
- It's already the second one?
- Today,
I think...
we have to figure out if the show is real or fake.
We have to focus on the show more than the food.
We're easily distracted by the food.
It looked so easy...
to make up the performance...
because the dishes were real.
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- Right?
- Right.
It was also weird that he used a handheld torch...
with that amazing wood fire next to him.
- Exactly!
- Yes, that was also suspicious.
He used that charcoal...
- Only in the beginning.
- Right?
He only used the torch after that.
The performance that he did seem like anyone could pull it off...
- after practice.
- Absolutely.
Right.
BIBI, did you find anything suspicious?
I was too distracted by the food.
- Oh, no.
- You paid attention to the food.
I couldn't notice anything else.
I'm sorry I'm not much help.
I was way too distracted.
- By the food?
- By the food.
I think I should be careful from now on.
I'll start training.
- How would you train?
- I'll train how to focus...
on other things with the food in front of me.
That won't be so easy.
Normally, I pay attention to the food with passion.
- Really?
- Yes.
I think we're near Hongdae.
We are.
- It's going to be a good show.
- Right.
I wonder what kind of show it is this time.
What would be the second place?
We'll find out.
What was the hint about the second show?
It was, "Something's moving!"
- "Something's moving."
- Right.
"It is moving!"
Do things move when they're not supposed to?
Magic? Could it be a magic cafe?
I wonder what it is.
- Let's get out.
- Thank you.
- Thank you for driving us.
- It was nothing.
(They arrive at the second venue with curiosity.)
The weather's pretty nice, considering it's summer.
- It's tolerable.
- Yes.
- The humidity is pretty low, so...
- Indeed.
- It's nice and dry.
- Yes.
- It's like the weather in LA.
- Exactly.
- The weather in LA.
- The sun is hot,
- but it's cool under a shade.
- Exactly.
I love it.
(They walk around the Hongdae area while enjoying the LA-like weather.)
Is this us?
- Now that the weather is nice...
- Goodness.
- Oh, boy.
- Where are you headed?
- I love the youthful energy.
- Yes.
How youthful.
- Drive safely!
- They even put on music.
- Are you going on a trip?
- Sorry?
- Yes!
- Have a safe trip!
- Bye!
How lovely.
- Wait, that's...
- "All lies."
(I didn't know)
I love it.
(He loves the song.)
I wanted to do that when I was in my 20s.
But you couldn't.
- I was too broke.
- You didn't have a car like that.
How nice is that, BIBI?
- I'm so jealous of them.
- It must be nice.
It was like they were paid actors.
You see a lot of these nowadays,
but everyone stared at you when you took the top off in the past.
- They did.
- Right?
Back then, people looked at you strangely,
even when you put on sunglasses.
- They did!
- Hello.
Hello.
Enjoy your food!
- Great.
- Mapo and Hongdae...
- are certainly...
- Right.
- youthful areas.
- Indeed.
- I see a lot of non-Koreans.
- And surprisingly...
(Noticing something)
- Is this it?
- Is it?
It just moved, right?
What is that? It moves.
Is this it?
- "Coffee?"
Why is it...
- opaque?
- It's opaque glass.
Is that how it usually is,
or did the crew do this?
I can't tell. Don't coffee shops usually...
- let you see...
- They're usually transparent.
- how many people there are?
- Right.
- It looks like an escape room.
- It does.
It's so suspicious from the outside.
- It's bizarre.
- A coffee shop...
- is supposed to be...
- Right.
It looks like they covered it.
(It's suspicious for many reasons.)
(What show will they watch here?)
I see a lot of Vincent van Gogh's works.
There are paintings.
(There are paintings?)
(As soon as they open the door,)
(they see framed paintings on the wall.)
Vincent van Gogh and...
(And a lot of them look familiar.)
(What do these famous paintings have to do with a show?)
- What?
That's so suspicious.
What?
It's "Mona Lisa".
What's wrong with her arm?
- This "Mona Lisa" is...
- It's trick art!
(This "Mona Lisa" looks normal at first glance,)
(but her arm is actually popping out of the painting.)
- This "Mona Lisa" is...
- It's trick art!
Trick art?
Oh, I see!
(Trick Art)
(An art piece that uses illusion...)
(to make a flat painting look three-dimensional)
I think you're supposed to take pictures like this with it.
(The greatest photo spot)
- Don't you think?
- Great job, BIBI.
- I didn't even think about that.
- Me neither.
- She's so youthful.
- She really is.
It's perfect for taking pictures.
(Glancing)
- Oh my goodness!
- What's wrong?
- I was so surprised.
- What is it?
(What's happening right now?)
Oh my!
Oh my gosh.
What are we going to do with this?
- Goodness!
- I can't...
This is really...
Gosh!
I don't think...
- So this is really...
- Wow!
You've got to be kidding!
This can't be real.
There's "The Fifer" here too.
"The Fifer".
"Girl with a Pearl Earring".
("Girl with a Pearl Earring" is on the other side.)
- And that's "The Gleaners".
- "The Gleaners".
Yes, it really is "The Gleaners".
(A Classic Paintings Cafe filled with various paintings)
(When you pass the suspicious "Mona Lisa",)
(you'll see the most unusual cafe you've ever seen.)
(This is where the show takes place.)
("The Gleaners" by Jean-Francois Millet)
("The Fifer" by Edouard Manet)
("Girl with a Pearl Earring" by Johannes Vermeer)
(It's a cafe where the paintings are alive and moving.)
So they just sit here like this for hours?
It makes no sense.
- Stop lying to us!
- This is fake!
- It's way too easy.
- This is so funny.
- This can't be real.
- Goodness.
- This must be it.
- Look, she's laughing.
She's holding in laughter.
You think this is funny too, right?
They were pushing it with this one. You have to agree.
- Right, miss?
- Wait...
- I mean...
- She'll have a crick in her neck.
- She's going to hurt herself.
- Exactly!
(Unbelievable)
- You should change poses.
- Right.
(Taking feedback in real time)
That other pose really strains the neck.
- Please move around.
- This is too easy.
(Please don't stay still.)
What is this?
- This place...
- It's too obvious.
- This place is perfectly fake.
- I know, right?
- You know, Byeon Woo Seok...
- Yes?
Woo Seok texted me the other day.
He said his friend's cafe will be featured on this show.
- Really?
- Could that be here?
- He said that?
- Yes.
Is that here?
(Is this a real cafe owned by Byeon Woo Seok's friend?)
Jae Seok, but this is all so suspicious.
- We have to be careful.
- Why don't we ask?
Woo Seok didn't tell me...
- what kind of cafe it was.
- Right.
(Could it be a trap Byeon Woo Seok set up with the crew?)
Let's ask the owner.
- Excuse me?
- Hello?
(They decide to talk to the owner first.)
Why is she doing this? I can't believe it.
She's even having trouble going through the door!
- Wait a minute.
- Stop it now!
Don't do this to us.
- Don't do this.
- Why?
- Why are they taking it this far?
- I'm telling you, stop it!
She can't go through.
(A rectangular figure steps inside with effort.)
(My gosh)
Don't do this.
- Why are they taking it this far?
- I'm telling you, stop it!
- Hello.
- This has to be fake.
- Right.
- Her voice is so gentle, though.
- I'm losing my mind.
- Nice to meet you.
Hello, I'm Oh Hui Jin. I'm 33,
and I run this classic paintings cafe.
It's a cafe where the subjects of classic paintings...
greet the customers and make the drinks themselves...
for an interactive experience.
(A cafe where the paintings are the baristas)
Back when I was travelling,
I saw many street performers...
with costumes and makeup.
Watching them made me realise...
I wanted to bring joy to others like them for a living too.
That's why I started this cafe.
At the beginning, we did...
"Self-Portrait with Bandaged Ear" by Vincent van Gogh,
and "Self-Portrait Dedicated to Dr. Eloesser" by Frida Kahlo.
Those were the 2 paintings we had in Season 1, so to speak.
Right now we're in Season Two, where we have...
"Girl with a Pearl Earring" by Johannes Vermeer,
"The Gleaners" by Jean-Francois Millet,
and "The Fifer" by Edouard Manet.
Yes, we do our makeup ourselves.
I taught and helped my staff with their makeup at first,
but now that they're used to it,
they do it themselves.
The most rewarding part is...
when the customers come and enjoy themselves.
And I have as much fun as they do...
whenever I get to surprise them properly.
I'm here!
"Mona Lisa" is making my coffee!
I took pictures with "The Fifer" too!
(I went last weekend too! The coffee here is great.)
(The cafe is already trending on social media.)
Sixth Sense crew, is this place real?
- An interactive paintings cafe?
- That's right.
Wait a minute...
I know four people are working here,
but you can't stay like this for hours. It's too hard.
We have a fixed schedule for performances like this.
- It's only from 1pm to 4pm.
- I see.
Even during the performance, we don't stay in fixed positions.
- We move around freely to talk...
- Oh, so you can move!
- and take pictures with customers.
- So you only pose...
- That's right.
- Okay.
- in between conversations.
- Yes.
- Then please start moving again.
- He's right.
- I beg you.
- You all must be tired.
Then do you always carry that frame on your back?
Yes, I try to have it on at all times.
We only perform a few hours a day,
and customers who couldn't make it in time...
might be disappointed.
So I always work with this frame.
You're a comedian, right?
- No way.
- I mean...
I have a feeling that you might be my junior.
- Are you sure?
- No, I'm not.
You said Byeon Woo Seok mentioned a cafe.
Do you happen to know Byeon Woo Seok?
No, I don't.
Is there another cafe like this?
- This mustn't be it.
- Right.
It's really cool that you're doing what you want to do in life.
(Is this theme-committed cafe real?)
(Jae Seok was looking at the part-timers.)
I noticed they can't stay still.
If you watch, they're like...
She's not meant for this part of the job.
(Back when they were talking to Hui Jin,)
(she kept meeting the members' eyes.)
(Bowing again)
So it seems to me...
this was made up suddenly to trick us.
- I agree.
- Right.
Don't you think?
Okay, then.
- Could we order some drinks first?
- Of course.
- Let's go to the counter.
- Thank you.
I really don't think she can move around with that frame.
- This is...
- Wow!
They have art lattes!
- Really?
- Art latte?
This is our signature menu.
(The paintings cafe's signature menu, art latte)
How does it work?
- This is your signature menu?
- Yes.
So we take a picture and send it to you through the QR code.
Then you can make a latte with that?
- That's right.
- Gosh.
- We have a printer, so...
- Goodness.
(Your picture taken with the painting...)
(becomes latte art.)
Should we all take a picture with "The Gleaners..."
- and print it on the latte?
- Gosh.
- Let's do it!
- Okay.
You look like Director Jang Hang Jun.
Really?
(Take pictures in a classic painting,)
So I just send you the picture like this?
(then send it.)
Should we order something else?
- Some cool drinks?
- I want iced americano.
- Goodness!
- What?
(One of the gleaners escaped.)
- Oh, gosh.
- One iced americano...
- My heart!
- Where are you going?
I have to help her.
- I see.
- So you come out to make drinks.
The others help out too.
One iced americano...
- And these are all cold, right?
- Yes.
It could be a production set.
Wait, why...
Why are you posing suddenly?
Take it easy. You can relax.
(Peeking)
I can't tell if the crew built this...
or if this is a real cafe.
Excuse me.
(The girl with the earring can't stay still.)
(This is ridiculous.)
What are you...
(I'm just posing in here.)
You're being the painting.
- You're one with the painting.
- Right.
This can't be an easy job.
- Posing, keeping up the act...
- Exactly.
And all the makeup.
I know there's a schedule,
but it's still hard, right?
- Oh, she pays you a lot?
- Really?
- It's good money?
- Money.
Then how does she make a profit?
Right?
She has to pay all her workers.
(BIBI thinks the salaries are too high to make a profit.)
But you never know these days.
Young folks these days...
might find this place enjoyable.
- Of course.
- Right.
(Pleased)
Do people come up and talk to you like this?
They do?
Do you reply?
Why don't you reply to us?
(Who are you talking to? I'm a painting.)
She went back.
They go back to being paintings when they're in a bind.
Back to being paintings.
- This is crazy.
- Goodness.
- Your drinks are ready.
- Thank you.
Gosh!
- Look!
- It's really there!
How does this even work?
It really looks like a classic painting.
- My goodness.
- I got it.
(The classic paintings cafe's signature menu)
- Gosh.
- I can't believe it's really there.
- It's just like the picture.
- This is amazing!
It's fascinating.
- It really looks like a drawing.
- This is so cool.
(The picture is reborn as a latte.)
Excuse me. Here are your art lattes.
- So many?
- Wow!
What is this?
So these are the art lattes?
- This is amazing.
- Our faces are...
My gosh!
Our faces are...
(Special art lattes for the Sixth Sense Crew)
- That's me!
- It's Mona Jae Seok.
- This is unbelievable.
- Wait...
This is "Girl with a Pearl Earring".
It's Song Eun I with a Pearl Earring.
- It's Frida Kahlo!
- Frida Kahlo.
- That's van Gogh's self-portrait.
- Right!
(BIBIda Kahlo and van Kyung Pyo's self-portraits)
- It's so pretty!
- That's van Gogh's self-portrait.
This painting is perfect for you, Hyeong Seo.
- I really like it.
- You go well with...
- Frida Kahlo's art.
- It looks amazing.
- So cool.
- Classic painting cakes.
- They're beautiful!
- So pretty.
It's "The Starry Night" by van Gogh.
(Classic paintings are recreated into cakes.)
That's Monet's "Water Lilies".
- These are van Gogh too.
- Right.
- I have something to say.
- Yes?
It's impossible to sell such high-quality cakes at this cost.
- It doesn't make sense.
- How much were these?
- 19 dollars.
- Yes.
- It's about that much.
- So...
She makes the drinks, performs,
and bakes these cakes herself? I don't buy it.
(Are these high-quality yet cheap cakes fake?)
Should we try them?
The latte is delicious.
- It really is.
- Yes.
It makes me think she really owns this cafe.
- Everything is tasty.
- I think so too.
It looks silly, so I didn't expect it to be good.
- But...
- It's really good!
The taste isn't silly at all.
What does this mean, then?
- It means she really runs a cafe.
- And I think...
she's confident in the quality of her drinks.
At this point, I want to grab whoever walks by...
and ask them if they think this place is real.
But they made sure people can't look inside.
- Right, you can't see a thing!
- Yes.
Most cafes have big windows...
- to bring people in.
- Exactly.
- That's right.
- Yes.
- I don't...
- Someone I know...
But with this cafe, they can't let people see.
Yes, people shouldn't look inside.
They'll just watch and leave.
That can never happen.
It does make sense,
considering what you just said.
- Right?
- I know.
- This latte especially...
- Yes.
- He really loves that latte.
- It's so...
It's delicious.
("If it's tasty, it's real!" Yu Jae Seok)
This is really tricky.
Do you think this is fake, BIBI?
I really think it is.
They don't even have a restroom.
Where is the restroom?
The restroom is this way.
I see. Is there a passcode?
No, just go right in.
Does your staff use the same restroom?
(Of course.)
You smiled so kindly while talking about the restroom.
He's so mellow.
What a mellow smile.
- Why don't we see the last show?
- Good idea.
- We've seen two so far.
- Yes.
Then we can decide which one is fake.
- Sounds good.
- Okay.
(The gleaner sensed they were wrapping up.)
She went up there again.
This is crazy.
She's posing again.
This is like "Night at the Museum".
- My goodness.
- Remember at the end...
when everything goes back to the way it was?
(Everyone went back to their place.)
This is absurd.
It's so funny.
- Thank you.
- Goodbye.
Thank you, ma'am.
(Bumping)
- The frame...
- Every time she bows...
- is hitting her!
- it hits her head!
I'm losing my mind.
It makes absolutely no sense!
(Awkward)
This is so fun.
- It's a really fun theme.
- Right.
I have no idea.
I can't tell if it's real or not.
This is so hard.
Shall we go?
(Off to the next place with great suspicion)
- Hello!
- Good afternoon.
- Hi there.
- Hello.
(They ran into some Gen Z on the way.)
Where are you headed?
Haidilao Hot Pot.
- Haidilao?
- Haidilao!
(The crew knows the restaurant too.)
(An impromptu hand-pulled noodles performance)
That's great.
(The noodles' POV)
- That's great.
- Kyung Pyo's good with the fans.
Haidilao!
(Perfect performance)
(We love you, Kyung Pyo!)
There are so many pretty shops.
- I know, right?
- It's nice.
It's amazing how they decorate so beautifully.
(The streets of Hongdae are filled with cute attractions.)
And it's so nice and windy today.
So cute.
(Feeling good)
This street makes me feel like I'm travelling abroad.
I know! I've never been on this street before.
I visit Hongdae occasionally too,
whether it's for a shoot or in my own time.
But I've never taken this route before either.
- Me too!
- Right.
Gosh, she's so youthful.
- Who?
- She gives off a youthful energy.
- How so?
- Her trendiness?
The colour scheme...
And she had a cool tattoo on her arm.
Hello.
(Walking by the trendy youngsters)
- Good afternoon.
- Hi.
I can't look at "Mona Lisa" the same way anymore.
- It's over there!
- My heart is pounding.
It says we can't trust her.
(A poster for a performance, "Don't trust Mona Lisa")
(Turning)
(Don't trust?)
Wait.
(What is this?)
Her smile is watching you.
Wait, is this...
(A poster with "Mona Lisa" is in the middle of the street?)
the B-Side?
You said there were hidden details.
(Exclaiming)
The hidden side!
- Is this it?
- Really?
Do you think we found it?
Is this like an easter egg?
- What do you think?
- I think so too!
Is this it? Is it?
Wait, or maybe it's an actual performance.
Premiering on July 7.
Art Hall...
- Faust Art Hall?
- Fouse?
- I don't know how to read this.
- Fox?
- Paus.
- Is this the B-Side?
This is...
Did we make an amazing discovery,
or is this a swing and a miss?
- It's just...
- Swinging and missing
(Swinging and missing)
(They move quickly after their short swing and a miss.)
- Hello.
- Good afternoon.
- What's that?
- It's a laser printer.
Gosh, this is...
They're printing on a wooden board.
(It's a laser wood shop that prints pictures on boards.)
What if there's a hidden clue in here too?
Imagine this finishes printing...
and the "The Fifer" is there.
- Gosh.
- Is this a B-Side?
- No way!
- Wait!
Don't trust "The Fifer"!
I'm sure it's not like that.
- This reminds me...
- I hope so.
of the oak scent from the barbecue place.
Why does it feel like everything is connected?
Right?
Is it?
(The members smell burning wood from a store they passed by.)
(Could this be a B-Side hidden by the production team?)
(They start being suspicious of everything.)
- We're looking really closely.
- Right?
- It's slowing us down.
- It's...
- I mean...
- We started walking really slowly.
I think those few coincidences...
- really got to us.
- Yes, we can't let it overwhelm us.
I just found another "Mona Lisa". Is this really a coincidence?
I just found another "Mona Lisa".
Is this really a coincidence? Gosh, I'm losing my mind.
- It's an upside-down "Mona Lisa".
- You're right.
Okay.
(Upside-down "Mona Lisa")
- Students in taekwondo uniforms.
- Taekwondo?
- Why do they seem fake to me too?
- They're here in groups.
They came out of nowhere.
(The members even start to suspect passersby.)
- They're not acting, right?
- Be careful!
(Crashing)
- Watch out!
- Goodness.
Are you all right?
(They're just students surprised to see celebrities.)
- Hello there.
- Good afternoon.
Hi!
Why does everything seem fake?
I feel the same way too.
I think this neighbourhood is weird.
Why do strange things keep happening?
Remember the convertible?
You don't run into so many students in uniform...
- in the afternoon these days.
- Exactly!
Are we here?
(While their suspicion grows,)
Boxing diet?
(they arrived at the next place.)
But I heard gunshots.
(Banging)
People are flying around.
(What was the gunshot sound in the recording tape?)
(Guns?)
Look, the world's first action performance pub!
(BIBI found a suspicious sign.)
Only here in Hongdae.
It's on the third floor!
This must be it.
Doesn't the sign look brand new, though?
- Right?
- The others look worn,
- but this one is shiny.
- Right.
- It's very suspicious.
- Yes.
(What show will be waiting for them here?)
- Why don't we go up first?
- Let's go.
(Exclaiming)
Is this it?
Oh, over here.
Come in at your reserved time.
(There's something on the door.)
The seats are first come, first served.
- People are jumping around?
- Yes.
(Is it a sign about the show?)
They must have an action-themed performance...
inside this place.
(They open the door and go inside.)
(Exclaiming)
It's really quiet.
(When you step inside the store,)
(you'll see a huge stage...)
(with various equipment for the show...)
(and a table that faces the stage.)
(What kind of performance will they see in here?)
Is this a performance?
Maybe it's like break dancing.
- They have a mat here.
- Right?
(Why is there a mat on the floor?)
They use mats for Taekwondo too.
Maybe that sound was a fist hitting a punch mitt.
It's similar, right?
(The recording tape)
(Punch mitts)
- Mitts can be loud.
- It could be from an action...
(Shouting)
I can't get used to this.
Goodness!
One, two! One, two!
Are they the same guys we met earlier?
(Coming in with loud chants...)
(are men in Taekwondo uniforms?)
- Wait!
- It's the same guys!
Are they?
Are they not?
- The uniform looks a bit different.
- It's not them.
They were younger than this.
- Okay.
- Yes.
Hold on.
Then did those guys just happen...
- to walk by us?
- Who were they?
(Meanwhile, the members got into their positions.)
This is so confusing.
(Shouting)
(Focus!)
(The Taekwondo performance began abruptly.)
Gosh.
This is a shop?
(Their Taekwondo group performance continues.)
- You can hear their uniforms.
- Right.
(Energetic)
(Tilting)
(Welcome to the Taekwondo show.)
(Break!)
Goodness.
It shattered into pieces!
(Amazed)
I wonder if his foot hurts.
This is so...
- My gosh.
- Goodness.
- My goodness.
- Gosh, it's scary.
- That cracking sound must be this.
- I guess so.
- The sound like gunshots.
- That's why it's flying around.
(This is basically a machine gun.)
(Exclaiming)
(Totally mesmerized)
(A consecutive 10-spin kick is coming up!)
Doesn't he get dizzy?
(Thank you!)
(Automatic round of applause)
- Is this a cafe?
- That does feel satisfying, though.
(Dazed)
(The show goes on.)
(More and more wooden boards)
(The K-breaking class where they smash everything)
So they just break them all like that.
(There's more!)
(Focused)
How is he going to break them?
(With a backflip)
Just like this!
Unbelievable!
That was so cool.
My goodness. This is...
- Are you the owner?
- Yes.
- Nice to meet you.
- Hello.
- Thank you for the great show.
- Are you okay?
- Yes.
We really enjoyed the show.
- We loved it.
- Thank you.
- Sir.
- Yes?
What kind of place is this?
We combined Taekwondo and a musical,
so you can dine while watching a show.
It's a Taekwondo musical pub.
Hello.
I'm Jeong Song Hwan,
the owner of this Taekwondo performance pub. Nice to meet you.
We used to train in Taekwondo together as friends,
and we wondered how to bring...
Taekwondo closer to the public.
Based on my experience performing...
in the military and overseas,
we decided to promote Taekwondo...
in a fun and exciting way.
(And that is how the Taekwondo show began.)
Our show is packed...
with cool board breaking and acrobatics.
A lot of foreign tourists visit us,
and we also get many families...
and couples on dates.
(A unique performance pub loved by families and couples)
Sixth Sense crew, do you think this place is real?
(Sixth Sense crew, do you think this place is real?)
I just don't get it.
- But this is...
- If I were here as a customer,
I wouldn't be able to focus on eating.
Mr. Jeong, how do customers usually react when they come here?
They say they leave feeling energized.
We also dance Taekwondo moves.
Okay.
We even do musical numbers...
- with a bit of acting added.
- Musical performances?
- Yes.
- I see.
(They also perform musical numbers with a touch of acting.)
Looking at the menu, it says...
A Bar of Song Tomato Pasta,
- Flying Kick Toowoomba Pasta, - Flying Kick Toowoomba Pasta.
- and Backflip Buffalo Wings.
- Backflip Buffalo Wings.
This is interesting.
Our most popular dishes are...
- the Flying Kick Toowoomba Pasta...
- Toowoomba.
and the Backflip Buffalo Wings.
- Then we'll have those.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
(Ordering the owner's recommendations)
(They've ordered some dishes for now, but...)
- Coming to the third place...
- It's more confusing, right?
I know. I think...
If I had to guess,
this place is... Stand-up comedy is popular these days, you know.
- Yes.
- A comedy venue?
I think they rented out...
- a stand-up comedy venue.
- That makes sense.
Right.
They just had to lay out mats...
and hire Taekwondo performers.
(Oh, right.)
(BIBI seems to have realised something.)
I go watch stand-up comedy all the time.
This place is so similar...
- to a stand-up comedy venue.
- It's similar, right?
- Exactly.
- Yes.
- You go everywhere, don't you?
- You really do.
I'm a huge stand-up comedy fan.
- Really?
- Yes.
(The new member with a packed schedule)
(Ding, ding)
- Your food is ready.
- Okay.
By the way, do you usually walk around barefoot like that?
Here are the Backflip Buffalo Wings you ordered.
Okay. Thank you.
(Where is he going?)
(The owner is heading to the stage after serving the food?)
- Again?
- My goodness.
Oh, dear.
(Busting out a backflip out of nowhere)
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
(Enjoy your meal.)
(What was that?)
This is why it's called Backflip Buffalo Wings.
(Ding, ding)
(The next dish is served.)
- What is this?
- This is Flying Kick Toowoomba.
- Flying Kick Toowoomba?
- No, please...
- He's heading over there.
My goodness.
(The textbook flying kick)
(Enjoy your meal!)
- It is really cool, though.
- It's amazing.
(It is cool and absurd at the same time.)
(Backflip Buffalo Wings)
(Flying Kick Toowoomba Pasta)
(And many more)
(Single-leg turn, neck slice, 540 kick)
(Confused)
They do seem like a demonstration team, though.
This just doesn't make sense.
Wait, this was made with ramyeon.
- What?
- You're right.
They used the ramyeon noodles.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
- They are ramyeon noodles.
- It's ramyeon.
(The noodles in the pasta are ramyeon?)
- This Toowoomba ramyeon...
- It's a thing.
- You did a commercial for it.
- You did.
I'll know right away once I taste it.
(Tasting it right away)
(The other members take a bite too.)
To add to that,
it really is the ramyeon I did the commercial for.
It is, isn't it?
This is ramyeon. I love it, though.
(A dish made with ramyeon on the menu?)
- Store-bought stuff tastes best.
- Store-bought food is good.
It's commercially made, so it suits my taste best.
That's right.
- You do have spot-on taste buds.
- Yes.
The food at that first place earlier felt too fancy...
and was just so-so,
but this place is perfect for my taste.
(I love it here.)
When you go to a stand-up comedy show,
- they sell beer and simple drinks.
- Things are simple.
The food there is strictly bar snacks.
(The food here is just pub grub.)
Simple bar bites you can snack on.
This fits the vibe perfectly.
It's great food to eat...
- while watching the show.
- Right. With some beer.
- It's good, right? My goodness.
- Yes.
How can anyone eat like this?
One, two.
(Not a replay of earlier)
How many wooden boards do they break a day?
Wooden boards are quite pricey.
- All day long...
- Right.
(Part 2 of the show begins.)
(Munching)
How many spins is that?
- Didn't he do four spins?
- That was amazing.
(Part 2 steps up the difficulty.)
(Nerve-racking for viewers)
I was scared he might crash.
I feel like I'm getting indigestion.
(Shouting)
I can't believe this.
They keep screaming while we're eating.
- We can't even eat in peace.
- I know.
- Gosh, this is...
- There are five boards.
Is he breaking them while walking through the air?
- Exactly.
- My goodness.
(An ultra-high-difficulty break)
(So satisfying!)
(A five-star board break!)
(The grand finale break)
That's pretty high up. They should be careful.
It looks over 3m high.
But this is...
(The finishing kick)
- Yes!
- Attention.
(The thrilling Taekwondo show, the end)
Bow.
- Enjoy your meal.
- Thank you.
(A polite finale befitting a polite martial art)
(This is too hard.)
The vibe isn't right for eating at all.
- This doesn't make sense.
- Not at all.
- This is absurd.
- Earlier,
we thought the second place was definitely fake.
But after seeing this, it was...
- Exactly.
- It seems plausible now, right?
(Confused)
Isn't this place way too weird?
It's beyond weird. It makes no sense.
They didn't even clean up these broken board pieces.
(A view of absolute chaos)
And they keep locking eyes having stare-downs with customers.
- Then they shout.
- They scream like this.
(Shouting)
(A taste of the original)
To me, they seem like...
a very famous Taekwondo demonstration team.
- Right.
- Their skills are insane.
I think so.
The ceiling here is lower...
than where they usually perform.
- Exactly.
- They're adjusting to this space.
That's right.
You can't do this unless you're a real pro.
Exactly.
(Jae Seok's guess: A fake show staged with a Taekwondo demo team)
First of all, if the stage takes up this much space,
- it won't pay off.
- Exactly.
- I think so.
- It doesn't make sense.
I just don't see how they profit.
(This is fake! Few tables for such a spacious stage)
(Can they actually turn a profit?)
But why do I keep feeling like...
- this place might be real?
- Why?
Because of the passion.
- You mean the owner?
- The passion of the owner.
I admire that passion and applaud it,
but look at the mess they left behind.
Traces of passion.
I mean, this is...
At a place like this, the owner and staff went inside,
leaving all this behind...
The two places from earlier were almost too easy.
Are we heading to make our pick now?
(The Taekwondo show)
Shall we go? This is way too tough.
It feels so fake that it's confusing.
This place looks fake, too.
This looks like a dance studio.
(Sixth Sense crew suspect everything until the very end.)
You're right. It is a dance studio.
(So suspicious)
Shall we gather our thoughts?
- Shall we do that?
- Yes.
The four of you need to agree...
- We do that?
- and make one single choice.
As for the penalty,
- we thought about a few options.
- Okay.
If you guessed wrong two weeks in a row,
you could do group costume dress-ups or stuff like that.
- Good.
- I like that.
All right.
- We dress up after the shoot ends?
- No.
- During next week's shoot.
- Right from the opening?
Sure. It has been a bit boring, right?
- Okay.
- I mean, the penalty.
Only if we get it wrong two weeks in a row, right?
- All right.
- My goodness.
Then, Hyeong Seo, what do you think?
Right. You have the freshest gut feelings here.
That's true.
I think it's the second place.
- The second one is fake.
- It's fake?
The clincher is that food and drink prices...
- The prices?
- just don't add up.
- You don't think it makes sense.
- No.
(The place that shocked everyone)
(A cafe taking its concept dead seriously)
(Shocked by famous painting costumes,)
(and shocked again by masterpiece desserts)
(The show...)
(with unbelievable paintings)
Be honest.
(Which batch of comedians did you debut with?)
(No. 2: Classic Paintings Cafe with Painting Show)
(It looks like it's no. 2.)
What do you think, CEO Song?
There's a chance the second place...
is fake, just as Hyoung Seo said.
Still, I wouldn't want to eat...
feeling so intimidated at number three.
It doesn't have a restaurant vibe.
If it were just a spot to sit back and enjoy a show,
I'd get it,
but eating in a place that looks as if a tornado just ripped through?
(A Taekwondo show pub where you can dine...)
(while watching a performance?)
(Yet the concept is a bit too extreme for enjoying a meal.)
(Is this a fake set in a rented comedy venue...)
(featuring a Taekwondo demonstration team?)
(No. 3: Taekwondo Musical Pub featuring Taekwondo Show)
All right, Kyung Pyo.
I actually think number one is fake.
- He's going down a different path.
- The thing is...
(A fire show enjoyed...)
(in the heart of the city)
(Pouring oil all over!)
(A 90-dollar-range course meal served alongside a fire show)
(Yet the price is lower than expected,)
(and the chef keeps vanishing mid-cooking.)
(No. 1: Urban Camping Concept Restaurant featuring Fire Show)
(Confused)
I'm torn between numbers 2 and 3.
But number three...
- But think of the passion...
- The passion?
The passion was real,
but what unfolded before our eyes...
was just too much of a mismatch for a restaurant.
Above all, the Taekwondo demonstration team...
and the space...
The ceiling height needed to be much taller.
- It should be at least this high.
- It should be this high.
Actually, even this is a bit too low.
- It should be taller.
- As high as two floors.
To execute high-performance moves.
So, what do we do?
(It's time to make a decision.)
Should we play rock-paper-scissors again today and...
- That's a lot of pressure.
- That's just so...
But what can we do?
- Isn't that just a bit too absurd?
- What do we do then?
Then let's bestow this glorious burden...
- upon our newcomer...
- That's a great idea!
- Let Hyeong Seo decide.
- BIBI, you choose it.
- Let's go with Hyeong Seo's pick.
- Yes.
Well... I don't want to.
- I don't want to.
- No.
If we fail consecutively and end up getting a penalty,
we won't...
Then it would all be your fault.
(Laughing)
We'll just grumble about it occasionally.
It's your very first day today, so you go ahead and decide.
Okay. I've...
actually had my heart set on number two this whole time.
- Okay.
- Okay. Let's keep it simple then.
I've never seen someone so full of conviction.
Okay.
This is the first episode of the long-awaited new season.
Which one is the fake? One, two, three!
- Number 2!
Ladies and gentlemen.
There has never been a show more shocking than this.
- Hey!
- Seriously?
Over the past six years...
Are they going this far?
We've thoroughly deceived you.
(The Set Remodelling Show: 52 times)
They've done it 52 times.
(The Fake Menu Development Show: 37 times)
They've developed a lot of fake menu items, too.
(AI, brands, meal kits, 2nd branches)
(Sixth Sense is back.)
(Sixth Sense: B-Side)
- It's Season 6.
- Season 6, B-Side.
It's B-Side. Entering its sixth year.
Please!
(It is back with truly authentic shows.)
All right.
(Will they be able to guess the correct answer from Episode 1?)
Please.
(Don't Believe It Show)
All right!
(Which is the single fake show?)
Please.
- What do we do, Kyung Pyo?
- My goodness.
Please.
(A nerve-wracking moment)
(Will they be able to guess the correct answer?)
I'm so scared!
- Fake!
- Please.
(Which is the single fake show?)
- What?
What is it?
(Which is the single fake show?)
(2. Classic Paintings Cafe)
(Fake)
- Yes! We got it!
- What? We got it right?
- We got it right!
- You did it!
This is unbelievable.
(Surprised)
(A round of applause)
Hyeong Seo!
- Isn't this a first?
- Right.
Isn't this the very first time we got it right in Episode One?
(The 1st time that they got it right as a group in Episode 1)
(A deep sigh of relief)
She said that...
- his passion seemed genuine.
- That's admirable.
How did you know?
BIBI has great intuition.
She said his passion was genuine.
- My goodness.
- So, we were so...
- It's unbelievable.
- I'm so relieved.
- Yes!
- That was great.
What a relief.
(Everyone, the show isn't over yet.)
- What?
(There's more?)
- My goodness!
- Gosh, what's that?
(What?)
- My goodness!
- Gosh, what's that?
(Who...)
(are you?)
Wait!
Those are the people we ran into on our way earlier!
It's those people from earlier.
- Earlier... I'm so startled.
- I just got goosebumps. What?
(Wait, these people are...)
(The Taekwondo group passed on the street)
Those foreign visitors from the convenience store!
- The convenience store! My gosh.
- My goodness. The store.
We met all of them earlier. They even called us handsome.
Hang on.
- The convenience store! My gosh.
- My goodness. The store.
(What on earth is happening?)
Wait. I got goosebumps.
(Goosebumps all over)
Right?
- I thought there were many people.
- I thought it was unusual.
(These people are today's B-Side.)
(If you're wondering who these people are...)
- Hello.
That's right!
- Yes!
- That's right!
- Right. It's them!
-They were there!
- I thought something was off.
- The convertible!
Even they were in on it?
(Shock and terror)
- The convertible!
- It was...
Even them?
(Even the ones in the convertible?)
I thought it was strange.
(The unusually large crowd of fans today)
- This is unbelievable.
- It's so scary.
Seriously.
(The production crew's accomplices)
I thought it was strange.
Right. "Lies" was playing.
You started preparing this 50 days ago?
What...
- Gosh, this is insane.
- My goodness.
- It's unbelievable.
- I've got goosebumps.
- How...
- There were 100 people?
There were as many as 100 people?
This is totally insane.
The reason we gathered you today...
is to provide clues to the cast.
(Today's B-Side: Plant 100 passers-by!)
My goodness.
No wonder today was strangely...
We'll divide and deploy you along the cast's moving routes.
Just become living clues, acting like NPCs.
(The 100 fake passers-by they encountered like that)
(This is...)
(Sixth Sense: B-Side Meets "The Truman Show.")
Right. It's "The Truman Show!"
- It's so terrifying.
- I'm really scared.
I know. This is insane.
(Then how were these people...)
(dropping clues about the answer?)
We will attach clues to your body.
(Clues?)
There's something written on the back.
- It says "Don't believe."
- "Don't believe."
(Letters attached one by one to the passers-by's clothes)
(Don't trust the Mona Lisa.)
It says, "Don't trust the Mona Lisa."
Gosh, this is crazy.
(Sighing)
How could anyone notice this?
(The foreigners in front of the convenience store)
- My goodness.
- "Classic Paintings Cafe."
This is so interesting.
(Even on the delivery man who brushed past at the cafe)
(Don't believe.)
"Don't believe."
- Look at that.
- My goodness.
(Shocked)
It's insane.
I had no idea.
- I didn't notice anything.
- I had no idea.
(Dumbfounded)
(And yet another hidden B-Side)
- They were there earlier.
- Yes.
We walked past here. That is the scene from earlier.
What does it say?
(We gave it all away.)
Where?
(Watch out for Mona Lisa.)
How were we supposed to see that?
Oh, that's annoying.
(Upset)
That's ridiculous.
(At the cafe during the opening)
- During the opening too?
- During the opening?
What was there?
(Did you notice?)
- "Art is fake."
(The answer was right on the wall.)
- I saw that poster.
- I saw it.
Right here.
(It was right under their noses.)
(In the alley)
(Don't trust Mona Lisa.)
That one!
(Wait. That is...)
- Hey. We saw that.
- We saw that.
(That was all designed by the production crew.)
(All those places they passed today)
- I've been saying it.
- Hello.
(9am)
What are you saying? You don't know them.
(Broaden your perspective...)
It's nice to be young.
(to see the other side of Sixth Sense.)
This is crazy.
(The B-Side Truman Show with 100 people)
That's crazy.
When it's so hot...
Thank you for your hard work when it's so hot.
- Well done.
Only if I'd known...
(100 helpers worked harder than anyone else.)
They had clues, and they practised hard.
But...
we thought they were just our fans, so we said hi...
and walked away.
I thought I'd become popular.
- I almost misunderstood...
- I thought things changed.
I almost showed off by mistake.
I almost showed off.
I'm shocked.
(Pretty shocked)
Can you break even?
- Can you?
- I'm not sure.
Seriously,
I didn't expect this much.
(Amazing scale)
Either way, I would've been shocked.
Thanks to everyone for joining us. Thank you.
- Thank you.
Thank you.
(Check out the official channel for the preparation process.)
(I got a call from the production crew.)
Next time...
(Extraordinary people will be coming.)
(So I'd better watch out not to get swept away.)
(Who are the guests that scare the members?)
(Energetic girls appear.)
(Chae Jeong An and Lee Ji Hye)
(How did you get close?)
(They went clubbing together.)
(Karaoke)
Okay mate.
(Okay.)
(Extraordinary from the start)
(Ji Hye also makes extraordinary deductions.)
(Sharp)
(I think two places are fake.)
(Only one)
(Only 1 of them is fake on this show.)
(The attention seeker is blunt.)
- Ji Hye...
- It wasn't me.
(Jae Seok makes a mistake while talking.)
(Don't talk with food in your mouth.)
(Helpless)
(By the way, this place...)
(costs a lot of inmate fund.)
(Inmate fund?)
(Trying to redeem herself)
(Along with spicy guests,)
(the crazy fake deal is coming.)
(Their crazy chemistry is coming soon.)